Sculpture Photograph Collection: Italy-United States
Yale University Arts Library
- Italy (Box 153)
  - Artists, Known., 3551 (Box 162)
    - O, 8 (Box 203)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 8 (Box 203)
        - Olivieri, Maffeo, 1484-1583., 1 (Box 203)
        - Orcagna, Andrea, 1308-1368., 5 (Box 203)
        - Orlandini, Amedeo, XX C., 1 (Box 203)
        - Ottini, Lorenzo, 1648-1736., 1 (Box 203)
    - P, 205 (Box 204)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 16 (Box 204)
        - Paernio, D., XVIII C., 1 (Box 204)
        - Paolozzi, Eduardo, XX C., 1 (Box 204)
        - Pazzi, Enrico, 1819-1899., 2 (Box 204)
        - Peruzzi, 1481-1536., 2 (Box 204)
        - Piccolomini Master, XV C., 4 (Box 204)
        - Pierino da Vinci, 1530-1553., 1 (Box 204)
        - Pistoletto, Michelangelo, 1933-., 1 (Box 204)
        - Pomodoro, Arnaldo, 1926-., 2 (Box 204)
        - Pomodoro, Gio, 1926-., 2 (Box 204)
      - Individual Artists., 189 (Box 204)
        - Pisano, Andrea, 1206-1280., 39 (Box 204)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 2 (Box 204)
          - Florence., 37 (Box 204)
            - Baptistry., 21 (Box 204)
            - Campanile., 16 (Box 204)
        - Pisano, Giovanni, c.1245-1314., 33 (Box 205)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 8 (Box 205)
          - Pisa., 14 (Box 205)
          - Pistoia., 11 (Box 205)
        - Pisano, Niccolo, 1220-1273., 75 (Box 205)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 2 (Box 205)
          - Perugia., 13 (Box 205)
            Many of these works are done with Giovanni Pisano.
          - Pisa., 30 (Box 205)
            - Pulpit overviews., 3 (Box 205)
            - Pulpit details., 16 (Box 205)
            - Pulpit panels: The Life of Christ., 11 (Box 206)
          - Siena., 31 (Box 206)
        - Pisano, Nino, active 1349-1368., 9 (Box 207)
        - Pollaiuolo, Antonio del, 1429-1498., 27 (Box 207)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 5 (Box 207)
          - Florence., 9 (Box 207)
          - Rome., 13 (Box 207)
        - Porta, Guglielmo della, active 1531-1557., 6 (Box 207)
    - Q, 67 (Box 208)
      - Individual Artists., 67 (Box 208)
        - Queirolo, Francesco, 1704-1762., 2 (Box 208)
        - Quercia, Jacopo della, 1367-1438., 65 (Box 208)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 13 (Box 208)
          - Bologna., 10 (Box 208)
          - Lucca., 16 (Box 208)
          - Siena., 26 (Box 208)
    - R, 315 (Box 209)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 16 (Box 209)
        - Raverti, Matteo, active c.1390-1436., 1 (Box 209)
        - Revezzano, Benedetto da, 1476-1556., 1 (Box 209)
        - Ricci, Stefano, 1765-1837., 2 (Box 209)
        - Rivalta, Augusto, 1837-1925., 1 (Box 209)
        - Romanelli, Mariano d'Agnolo, active 1372-1390., 1 (Box 209)
        - Romano, Giovanni Cristoforo, active 1470-1512., 2 (Box 209)
        - Rossi, Angelo de, 1671-1715., 1 (Box 209)
        - Rossi, Vicenzo de', 1525-1587., 2 (Box 209)
        - Rosso, Medardo, 1858-1928., 1 (Box 209)
        - Rubatto, Carlo, 1810-1891., 1 (Box 209)
        - Rufolo, Niccolo, active 1272., 1 (Box 209)
        - Ruggero di Amalfi, active 1111., 1 (Box 209)
        - Rutelli, Mario, 1859-1941., 1 (Box 209)
      - Individual Artists., 299 (Box 209)
        - Ricciarelli, 1509-1566., 2 (Box 209)
          Also known as Daniele da Volterra.
        - Rizzo, Antonio, 1465-1499., 10 (Box 209)
        - Robbia, della, Workshop of., 36 (Box 210)
        - Robbia, Andrea della, 1435-1525., 43 (Box 210)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 27 (Box 210)
          - Florence., 16 (Box 210)
        - Robbia, Giovanni della, 1469-1529., 22 (Box 211)
        - Robbia, Lucca della, 1399-1482., 104 (Box 211)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 18 (Box 211)
          - Florence., 86 (Box 211)
            - Miscellaneous locations., 41 (Box 211)
            - Bargello (National Museum)., 12 (Box 212)
            - Cathedral Museum, Cantoria., 29 (Box 212)
            - Or San Michele., 4 (Box 212)
        - Roccatagliata, Niccolo, c.1580-1635., 5 (Box 212)
        - Rossellino, Antonio, 1427-1479., 75 (Box 213)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 28 (Box 213)
          - Florence., 39 (Box 213)
          - Naples., 8 (Box 213)
        - Rossellino, Bernardo, 1409-1464., 14 (Box 214)
        - Rusconi, Camillo, 1658-1728., 5 (Box 214)
          Includes a portrait bust of Camillo by Giuseppe Rusconi.
        - Rustici, Giovanni Francesco, 1474-1554., 3 (Box 214)
    - S, 133 (Box 214)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 14 (Box 214)
        - Saccomanno, Santo, 1833-1914., 2 (Box 214)
        - Salvestrini and Pierotti, XVII C.?, 1 (Box 214)
        - San Gallo, Guiliano da, 1445/52-1516., 3 (Box 214)
        - Santucci, Agostino, ?., 1 (Box 214)
        - Scanzi, XIX C., 1 (Box 214)
        - Severo da Ravenna, active c.1500., 2 (Box 214)
        - Somaini, Francesco, 1926-., 1 (Box 214)
        - Spinazzi, Innocenzo, -1798., 1 (Box 214)
        - Stagi, Stagio, c.1496-1563., 2 (Box 214)
      - Individual Artists., 119 (Box 214)
        - Sammartino, Giuseppe, 1720-1793., 5 (Box 214)
        - San Gallo, Francesco di, 1494-1576., 5 (Box 214)
        - Sanmichele, Michele, 1484-1559., 7 (Box 214)
          Works done with Simone and Francesco Mosca.
        - Sano di Matteo, -1434., 3 (Box 214)
          Works done with Luca di Giovanni, active 1384-1390.
        - Sansovino, Andrea, 1460-1529., 38 (Box 215)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 13 (Box 215)
          - Florence., 11 (Box 215)
          - Rome., 14 (Box 215)
        - Sansovino, Jacopo, 1477-1570., 22 (Box 215)
        - Santa Croce, Girolamo da, active 1520-1529., 3 (Box 215)
        - Sant'Agata, Francesco da, active 1520., 16 (Box 215)
        - Scalza, Ippolito, c.1532-1617., 3 (Box 216)
        - Silvestro di Giacomo di Solmona, ?., 5 (Box 216)
        - Solari, Cristoforo, c.1460-1527., 5 (Box 216)
        - Susini, Antonio, -1624., 7 (Box 216)
    - T, 36 (Box 216)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 12 (Box 216)
        - Tadolini, Scipione, 1822-1892., 1 (Box 216)
        - Tantardini, Antonio, 1829-1879., 1 (Box 216)
        - Tasso Giovanni Battista del, 1500-1555., 2 (Box 216)
        - Tasso, Leonardo del, 1466-1500., 2 (Box 216)
        - Tavani, Giovanni, 1934-., 1 (Box 216)
        - Tribolo, Il, 1485-1550., 4 (Box 216)
        - Trombetta, E., XIX C., 1 (Box 216)
      - Individual Artists., 24 (Box 216)
        - Tacca, Pietro, 1580-1650., 6 (Box 216)
        - Tino di Camaino, c.1285-1337., 9 (Box 216)
        - Torrigiani, Pietro, 1492-1522., 5 (Box 216)
        - Turini, Giovanni di, 1841-1899 (?)., 4 (Box 216)
    - U, V, 133 (Box 217)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 12 (Box 217)
        - Urbano da Cortona, 1426-1504., 3 (Box 217)
        - Valdambrino, Francesco di Domenico, active 1409-1426., 1 (Box 217)
        - Vanni, Alberto, 1906-., 4 (Box 217)
        - Vargnand, XVI C.?, 1 (Box 217)
        - Vasari, Giorgio, 1512-1574., 2 (Box 217)
        - Vicentini, Vincenzo, XVI C., 1 (Box 217)
      - Individual Artists., 121 (Box 217)
        - Vecchietta, Il, 1412-1480., 13 (Box 217)
          Also known as Lorenzo di Pietro.
        - Vela, Vincenzo, 1820-1891., 3 (Box 217)
        - Verocchio, Andrea del, 1435-1488., 83 (Box 217)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 18 (Box 217)
          - Florence., 48 (Box 217)
            - Miscellaneous locations., 4 (Box 217)
            - Bargello (National Museum)., 22 (Box 217)
              - Miscellaneous subjects., 10 (Box 217)
              - David., 12 (Box 217)
            - Or San Michele., 6 (Box 218)
            - San Lorenzo., 16 (Box 218)
              - Miscellaneous subjects., 3 (Box 218)
              - Medici Tomb., 13 (Box 218)
          - Venice., 17 (Box 218)
        - Vinci, Pierino da, 1530-1553., 3 (Box 218)
        - Vittorio, Alessandro, 1524-1608., 19 (Box 218)
    - W, X, Y, Z, 6 (Box 218)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 6 (Box 218)
        - Wildt, Adolfo, 1868-1931., 2 (Box 218)
        - Ximenes, 1855-1927., 1 (Box 218)
        - Zandomeneghi, Luigi, (1778-1850) and Pietro, (1806-1866)., 1 (Box 218)
        - Zironi and Liberati, ?., 1 (Box 218)
        - Zotto, Antonio da, active 1879., 1 (Box 218)
- Japan (Box 219)
  - Known Artists, A-Z., 4 (Box 219)
    - Kubota, Shigeko, 1937-., 1 (Box 219)
    - Kusama, Yayoi, 1929-., 1 (Box 219)
    - Nagare, Masayuki, XX C., 1 (Box 219)
    - Yamaguchi, Katsuhiro, XX C., 1 (Box 219)
- Jugoslavia (Yugoslavia). (Box 220)
  - Anonymous Artists., 4 (Box 220)
    - Romanesque., 1 (Box 220)
    - XII-XIII C., 3 (Box 220)
  - Known Artists, A-Z., 23 (Box 220)
    - Mestrovic, Ivan, 1883-1962., 20 (Box 220)
    - Rosandic, Toma, XX C., 3 (Box 220)
- Norway (Box 220)
  - Anonymous Artists., 22 (Box 220)
    - Pre-X Century., 3 (Box 220)
    - XII Century., 5 (Box 220)
    - XIII Century., 10 (Box 220)
    - XIV Century and later., 4 (Box 220)
  - Known Artists, A-Z., 1 (Box 220)
    - Rasmussen, Wilhelm, XIII C.?, 1 (Box 220)
- Poland (Box 220)
  - Known Artists., 2 (Box 220)
    - Maucher, Christopher, 1642-1705., 1 (Box 220)
    - Wittig, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 220)
- Portugal (Box 220)
  - Anonymous Artists., 16 (Box 220)
  - Known Artists., 12 (Box 220)
    - Loguin, Jacques, -1559., 12 (Box 220)
      Some works done with Nicolas Chanterene, active 1517-1551.
- Rumania (Box 221)
  - Known Artists., 46 (Box 221)
    - Brancusi, Constantin, 1876-1957., 45 (Box 221)
    - Brauner, Victor, 1903-1966., 1 (Box 221)
- Russia (Box 221)
  - Anonymous Artists., 8 (Box 221)
    - Romanesque., 8 (Box 221)
  - Known Artists., 82 (Box 221)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, A-Z., 8 (Box 221)
      - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1907-1981., 1 (Box 221)
      - Ermilov, Vassily, 1894-1968., 1 (Box 221)
      - Kabakov, Ilya, 1933-., 1 (Box 221)
      - Kakabadze, David, 1890-., 1 (Box 221)
      - Malevich, Kasimir, 1878-1935., 1 (Box 221)
      - Meduniezky, Kasimir, c.1899-., 1 (Box 221)
      - Rodchenko, Alexander, 1891-1956., 1 (Box 221)
      - Shar, Ivan, 1890-., 1 (Box 221)
    - Individual Artists., 74 (Box 221)
      - Archipenko, Alexander, 1887-1967., 17 (Box 221)
      - Derujinsky, Gleb, 1888-., 1 (Box 221)
      - Gabo, Naum, 1890-1977., 15 (Box 222)
      - Pevsner, Antoine, 1886-1962., 18 (Box 222)
      - Tatlin, Vladimir, 1885-1953., 9 (Box 222)
      - Troubetzkoy, Prince Paul, 1866-1938., 1 (Box 222)
      - Zadkine, Ossip, 1890-., 13 (Box 222)
- Spain (Box 223)
  - Anonymous Artists., 174 (Box 223)
    - Miscellaneous., 10 (Box 223)
    - XI Century., 5 (Box 223)
    - XII Century., 40 (Box 223)
    - XIII Century., 28 (Box 223)
    - XIV Century., 28 (Box 224)
    - XV Century., 24 (Box 224)
    - XVI Century., 11 (Box 224)
    - XVII Century., 19 (Box 225)
    - XVIII Century., 9 (Box 225)
  - Known Artists., 394 (Box 225)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, A-Z., 35 (Box 225)
      - Arnau de Bruselas, active 1549-1552., 1 (Box 226)
      - Artesa de Segre, XIII C., 1 (Box 226)
      - Blanquer, Jaime, active 1600-1627., 1 (Box 226)
      - Dancart, Pieter, -c.1487., 1 (Box 226)
      - Forment, Damian, 1480-1541., 1 (Box 226)
      - Gamiz, Pedro Lopez de, active 1557-1587, 2 (Box 226)
      - Gomar, Francisco, 1433-1493., 1 (Box 226)
      - Gonzalez, Julio, 1876-1942., 1 (Box 226)
      - Gris, Juan, 1887-1927., 1 (Box 226)
      - Haya, Rodrigo de la, and Martin, active 1562-1580., 1 (Box 226)
      - Laboria, Pedro de, active 1739-1749., 1 (Box 226)
      - Larrea y Ercilla, Lope de, 1540-1623., 1 (Box 226)
      - Lobo, Baltasar, 1910-., 2 (Box 226)
      - Melida, Arturo, XIX C., 1 (Box 226)
      - Millan, Pedro, XV C., 2 (Box 226)
      - Mora, Jose de, 1642-1724., 1 (Box 226)
      - Navarro, Juan de, XVI C., 2 (Box 226)
      - Ordonez, Bartolome, -1520., 1 (Box 226)
      - Pere, Johan, XV C., 1 (Box 226)
      - Pesquera, Diego de, ?., 1 (Box 226)
      - Peti Juan, XVI C., 1 (Box 226)
        Work done with Diego Copin.
      - Prado, Mateo de, -1677., 1 (Box 226)
      - Quadra, Pedro de, XVII C., 1 (Box 226)
      - Ribot, Domingo Talarn, XIX C., 1 (Box 226)
      - Roldan, Maria Luisa, 1656-1704., 1 (Box 226)
      - Roldan, Pedro, 1624-1699., 2 (Box 226)
      - Solis, Francisco de (?), 1629-1684., 1 (Box 226)
      - Vallejo, Juan de, active 1512-1569., 1 (Box 226)
      - Vallfogona, Pedro Juan, XV C., 2 (Box 226)
    - Individual Artists, A-Z., 359 (Box 226)
      - Apriles de Carona, Antonius Maria de, XVI C., 3 (Box 226)
      - Berruguete, Alonso, 1489-1561., 16 (Box 226)
      - Cano, Alonso, 1601-1667., 15 (Box 226)
      - Chillida, Eduardo, 1924-., 6 (Box 226)
      - Churriguera, Jose Benito de, 1665-1725., 2 (Box 226)
      - Cornejo, Pedro Duque, -1758., 22 (Box 226)
      - Dali, Salvador, 1904-1989., 4 (Box 226)
      - Fancelli, Domenico, 1469-1519., 8 (Box 227)
      - Fernandez, Gregorio, 1576-1636., 13 (Box 227)
      - Gonzalez, Julio, 1876-1942., 9 (Box 227)
      - El Greco, 1545-1614., 8 (Box 227)
      - Juni, Juan de, c.1507-1577., 10 (Box 227)
      - Leoni, Pompeo, 1533-1608., 8 (Box 227)
      - Manolo, 1872/6-1945., 2 (Box 228)
        Also known as Manuel Martinez Hugue.
      - Master Aloy, XIV C., 2 (Box 228)
      - Master Bartholomew, XIV C., 2 (Box 228)
      - Mena y Escalante, Alonso, 1587-1646., 4 (Box 228)
      - Mena y Medrano, Pedro de, 1628-1688., 24 (Box 228)
      - Mesa, Juan de, 1583-1627., 3 (Box 228)
      - Miro, Joan, 1893-1983., 14 (Box 228)
      - Montanes, Juan Martinez, 1568-1649., 60 (Box 229)
      - Peral, Torcuato Ruiz del, 1708-1773., 2 (Box 229)
      - Pereira, Manuel, 1574-1667., 2 (Box 229)
      - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973., 51 (Box 230)
      - Risueno, Jose, 1665-1732., 7 (Box 230)
      - Rueda, Teodosio Sanchez de, 1677- before 1731., 2 (Box 230)
      - Siloe, Diego de, c.1495-1563., 12 (Box 230)
      - Siloe, Gil de, XV C., 16 (Box 231)
      - Vazquez y Hernandez, Juan Bautista, active 1570-1601., 15 (Box 231)
      - Vigarny, Felipe, c.1470-1543., 10 (Box 231)
      - Zarcillo y Alcaraz, Francisco, 1707-1783., 5 (Box 231)
      - Zarza, Vasco de la, -1524., 2 (Box 231)
- Sweden (Box 232)
  - Anonymous Artists., 14 (Box 232)
  - Known Artists., 180 (Box 232)
    - Miscellaneous Artists., 6 (Box 232)
      Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippngs.
      - Fonssagrives-Penn, Lisa, 1911-1992., 1 (Box 232)
      - Gullesson, Haken, XVI C., 1 (Box 232)
      - Heyde, Henning von der, XVI C., 2 (Box 232)
      - Jacobsen, XX C., 1 (Box 232)
      - Junge, Johannes, XV C., 1 (Box 232)
    - Individual Artists., 174 (Box 232)
      - Milles, Carl, 1875-1955., 174 (Box 232)
        - Miscellaneous works., 56 (Box 232)
        - Diana Fountain., 10 (Box 233)
        - Europa Fountain., 15 (Box 233)
        - Folkunga Fountain., 4 (Box 233)
        - Fountain of Industry., 2 (Box 233)
        - Harrisburg Doors., 1 (Box 233)
        - Jonah Fountain., 5 (Box 233)
        - Meeting of the Waters Fountain., 3 (Box 233)
        - Orpheus Fountain., 35 (Box 233)
        - Peace Monument., 6 (Box 234)
        - Poseidon Monument., 23 (Box 234)
        - Rudbeckius Monument., 4 (Box 234)
        - Sea God., 4 (Box 234)
        - Sunglitter., 6 (Box 234)
- Switzerland (Box 235)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous folders.
  - Anonymous Artists., 10 (Box 235)
  - Known Artists., 76 (Box 235)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, A-Z., 17 (Box 235)
      - Aeschbacher, Hans, 1906-1980., 1 (Box 235)
      - Bill, Max, 1908-., 3 (Box 235)
      - Bloc, Andre, XX C., 2 (Box 235)
      - Germann-Jahn, Charlotte, 1921-., 1 (Box 235)
      - Gilioli, Emile, 1911-., 1 (Box 235)
      - Oppenheim, Meret, 1913-1986., 3 (Box 235)
      - Raetz, Markus, 1941-., 1 (Box 235)
      - Seligman, K., 1900-., 1 (Box 235)
      - Spoerri, Daniel, 1930-., 1 (Box 235)
      - Taeuber-Arp, Sophie, 1889-1943., 2 (Box 235)
      - Zschokke, Alexander, 1894-., 1 (Box 235)
    - Individual Artists, A-Z., 59 (Box 235)
      - Giacometti, Alberto, 1901-1966., 51 (Box 235)
      - Tinguely, Jean, 1925-1991., 8 (Box 235)
- Latin America (Box 236)
  - Miscellaneous countries., 9 (Box 236)
    - Anonymous Artists., 1 (Box 236)
    - Known Artists., 5 (Box 236)
      - Caban, Flores, XIX C., 1 (Box 236)
      - Castro-Cid, Enrique, 1937-., 2 (Box 236)
      - Matta-Echaurren, Roberto S., 1911-., 1 (Box 236)
      - Rafael, Jesus, 1923-., 1 (Box 236)
  - Argentina., 8 (Box 236)
    - Anonymous Artists., 1 (Box 236)
    - Known Artists, A-Z., 7 (Box 236)
      - Fioravanti, Jose, XX C., 1 (Box 236)
      - Jaurez, Horacio, XX C., 1 (Box 236)
      - Lagos, Alberto, XX C., 1 (Box 236)
      - Minujin, Marta, 1943-., 3 (Box 236)
      - Sibellino, Antonio, XX C., 1 (Box 236)
- Bolivia, 2 (Box 236)
  - Anonymous Artists., 1 (Box 236)
  - Known Artists., 1 (Box 236)
    - Montanes, Martinez, Colonial period., 1 (Box 236)
  - Brazil, 8 (Box 236)
    - Known Artists., 8 (Box 236)
      - Lisboa, Antonio Francisco, XVIII-XIX C., 5 (Box 236)
      - Maria, 1900-., 3 (Box 236)
        Also known as Maria Martins.
  - Colombia., 10 (Box 236)
    - Anonymous Artists., 6 (Box 236)
    - Known Artists., 4 (Box 236)
      - Botero, Fernando, 1932-., 1 (Box 236)
      - Laboria, Pedro, Colonial period., 2 (Box 236)
      - Villamizar, Ramirez, 1923-., 1 (Box 236)
  - Costa Rica., 1 (Box 236)
    - Known Artists., 1 (Box 236)
      - Jimenez, Max, XX C., 1 (Box 236)
  - Cuba., 3 (Box 236)
    - Known Artists., 3 (Box 236)
      - Blanco, Teodoro Ramos, XX C., 1 (Box 236)
      - Mendieta, Ana, 1948-1983., 2 (Box 236)
  - Ecuador., 1 (Box 236)
    - Anonymous Artists., 1 (Box 236)
  - Mexico., 49 (Box 237)
    - Anonymous Artists., 40 (Box 237)
    - Known Artists., 9 (Box 237)
      - Balbas, Jeronimo de, XVIII C., 1 (Box 237)
      - Tolsa, Manuel, 1757-1816., 8 (Box 237)
  - Peru., 21 (Box 237)
    - Anonymous Artists., 20 (Box 237)
    - Known Artists., 1 (Box 237)
      - Gavilan, Baltasar, ?., 1 (Box 237)
- Canada (Box 237)
  - Known Artists., 2 (Box 237)
    - Harvey, XX C., 1 (Box 237)
    - Murray, Robert Gray, 1936-., 1 (Box 237)
- United States (Box 238)
  - Anonymous Artists., 94 (Box 238)
    - Pre-XVIII Century or Undated., 5 (Box 238)
    - XVIII Century., 20 (Box 238)
    - XIX-XX Century., 69 (Box 238)
  - Known Artists., 1743 (Box 239)
    - A, 72 (Box 239)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 28 (Box 239)
        - Acconci, Vito, 1940-., 2 (Box 239)
        - Adams, Dennis, 1948-., 2 (Box 239)
        - Africano, Nicholas, 1948-., 1 (Box 239)
        - Agam, Jacob, 1928-., 3 (Box 239)
        - Ajay, Abe, 1919-., 1 (Box 239)
        - Albert, Calvin, XX C., 1 (Box 239)
        - Ames, Alexander, XIX C., 1 (Box 239)
        - Amateis, Louis, 1855-c.1913., 1 (Box 239)
        - Amino, Leo, 1911-., 1 (Box 239)
        - Andre, Carl, 1935-., 2 (Box 239)
        - Ant Farm, XX C., 1 (Box 239)
        - Antonakos, Stephen, 1926-., 1 (Box 239)
        - Arneson, Robert, 1930-., 3 (Box 239)
        - Arnold, Anne, 1925-., 4 (Box 239)
        - Artschwager, Richard, 1924-., 1 (Box 239)
        - Asher, Michael, 1943-., 1 (Box 239)
        - Aycock, Alice, 1946-., 2 (Box 239)
      - Individual Artists., 44 (Box 239)
        - Adams, Herbert, 1858-1945., 4 (Box 239)
        - Agostini, Peter, 1913-., 4 (Box 239)
        - Aitken, Rovert, 1878-1949., 4 (Box 239)
        - Amateis, Edmond, 1897-., 3 (Box 239)
        - Angel, John, XIX-XX C., 25 (Box 239)
        - Augur, Hezekiah, 1791-1858., 4 (Box 239)
    - B, 106 (Box 240)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 47 (Box 240)
        - Bailly, Joseph A., 1825-1883., 1 (Box 240)
        - Ball, Thomas, 1819-1911., 3 (Box 240)
        - Barnard, George Grey, 1863-1938., 1 (Box 240)
        - Barney, Matthew, XX C., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bartlett, Truman Howe, 1835-1923., 1 (Box 240)
        - Baskin, Leonard, 1922-., 2 (Box 240)
        - Batchelder, Evelyn B. Longman, 1874-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bates, Gladys Edgerly, 1898-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Beach, Chester, 1881-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Beckman, William, 1942-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Beecher, Laban S., XIX C., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bell, Larry, 1939-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bell, Solomon, XIX C., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bellamy, John, ?., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bermudez, Ramon, XX C., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bertoia, Harry, 1915-1978., 3 (Box 240)
        - Biederman, Charles, 1906-., 2 (Box 240)
        - Billings, Hammatt, 1818-1874., 2 (Box 240)
        - Black, Calvin, 1903-1972., 1 (Box 240)
        - Boghosian, Varujan, 1926-., 3 (Box 240)
        - Bohnert, Thom, 1948-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Bontecou, Lee, 1931-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Borofsky, Jonathan, 1942-., 4 (Box 240)
        - Bottiau, A., XX C., 1 (Box 240)
        - Brainard, Joe, 1942-., 2 (Box 240)
        - Brecht, George, 1926-., 1 (Box 240)
        - Browere, John H. I., 1792-1834., 2 (Box 240)
        - Brown, William Kirke, 1814-1886., 3 (Box 240)
        - Burden, Chris, 1945-., 2 (Box 240)
        - Butterfield, Deborah, 1949-., 1 (Box 240)
      - Individual Artists., 59 (Box 240)
        - Baizerman, Saul, 1889-1957., 3 (Box 240)
        - Barnard, George Gray, 1863-1938., 6 (Box 240)
        - Barthe, Richard, 1901-., 2 (Box 240)
        - Bartlett, Paul Wayland, 1865-1925., 21 (Box 240)
        - Benglis, Lynda, 1941-., 4 (Box 241)
        - Ben-Shmuel, Ahron, 1903-., 2 (Box 241)
        - Bitters, Karl, 1867-1915., 2 (Box 241)
        - Blazys, Alexander, 1894-., 3 (Box 241)
        - Borglum, Gutzon, 1867-1941., 9 (Box 241)
        - Borglum, Solon, 1868-1922., 2 (Box 241)
        - Bourgeous, Louise, 1911-., 5 (Box 241)
    - C, 158 (Box 241)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 31 (Box 241)
        - Cadorin, Ettore, 1876-., 1 (Box 241)
        - Caesar, Doris, 1892-1971., 1 (Box 241)
        - Calverley, Charles, 1832-1914., 1 (Box 241)
        - Carlton, Brents, XX C., 1 (Box 241)
        - Carr, Thomas, XIX C., 1 (Box 241)
        - Cerracchi, Giuseppe, 1751-1801., 2 (Box 241)
        - Chamberlain, David, XX C., 1 (Box 241)
        - Chase, Lila Elizabeth, 1892-., 1 (Box 241)
        - Chase-Riboud, Barbara, 1936-., 2 (Box 241)
        - Chicago, Judy, 1939-., 3 (Box 241)
        - Chryssa, 1933-., 4 (Box 241)
        - Clark, Walter L., XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 241)
        - Clarke, Fred B., active 1929., 1 (Box 241)
        - Clevenger, Shobal Vail, 1812-1843., 1 (Box 241)
        - Cohen, Barry, 1934-., 1 (Box 241)
        - Coletti, Joseph, 1898-., 1 (Box 241)
        - Conner, Bruce, 1933-., 1 (Box 241)
        - Cox, Kenyon, 1856-1919., 1 (Box 241)
        - Cullery, Mary, XX C., 1 (Box 241)
        - Curran, Don E., XX C., 1 (Box 241)
        - Cutler, Charles, XX C., 1 (Box 241)
      - Individual Artists., 127 (Box 242)
        - Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976., 56 (Box 242)
          - Miscellaneous subjects., 10 (Box 242)
          - Animals., 11 (Box 242)
          - Mobiles., 35 (Box 242)
            - Hanging., 19 (Box 242)
            - Standing., 16 (Box 242)
        - Calder, A. Stirling, 1870-1945., 4 (Box 242)
        - Callery, Mary, 1903-1977., 8 (Box 242)
        - Campbell, Kenneth, 1913-1986., 2 (Box 242)
        - Cecere, Gaetano, 1894-., 1 (Box 242)
        - Chamberlain, John, 1927-., 8 (Box 243)
        - Clark, Allen, 1896/8-1950., 4 (Box 243)
        - Cornell, Joseph, 1903-1973., 20 (Box 243)
        - Crawford, Thomas, 1813-1857., 11 (Box 243)
          Includes a folder of miscellaneou clippings.
        - Creeft, Jose de, 1884-1982., 13 (Box 243)
    - D, 91 (Box 243)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 23 (Box 243)
        - Davies, John, 1946-., 1 (Box 243)
        - De Andrea, John, 1941-., 3 (Box 243)
        - De Coux, Janat, 1904-., 2 (Box 243)
        - De Kooning, Willem, 1904-1997., 1 (Box 243)
        - De Maria, Walter, 1935-., 3 (Box 243)
        - Demetrios, Aristedes, 1932-., 4 (Box 243)
        - Diederich, Hunt, 1884-., 1 (Box 243)
        - Diller, Burgoyne, 1906-1965., 1 (Box 243)
        - Dowler, Charles, XIX C., 1 (Box 243)